Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - New Directions for the School of Education, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - McKay Report, undated (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 268 9
  - Sub-Committee to Study Student Press, 1969-1970 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - A Study of Management Information Systems Planning, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - NYSESE - Realities and Perspectives in Education, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Education Conference, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - NYC Department of Correction Project, 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Plan for Developing Trainers of Nonprofessionals - Riessmann, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Position Description (Vice Dean), 1965 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Reogranization of School of Education into Divisions, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Senate Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Hester's Report to Senate, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Admissions and Registration, 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Rating Forms, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Model School for City Children, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Project APEX, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - National Institute for Teacher Education AACTE, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - NYS & NYU Meeting - Potential Relationships, undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - NYS Citizens Committee for Public Schools, undated (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - NYS Education Department Visitation, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - NCATE General, undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Mission of the School - faculty reactions, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Hester - Academic Goals and Financial Needs, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - School of Education Report of Special Committee to Implement McKay Report, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Appendix, undated (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Blue Prints - A New School Washington Square, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 269 7
  - Yellow Envelope - Photographs, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Yellow Envelope - Diamond Jubilee Dinner, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Yellow Envelope - UNESCO, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Yellow Envelope - Zian Profile, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Organizers, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - School of Education, Study IV, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Picket Music Sheets, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Teaching Effectiveness and Government Awards, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Students Activism, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Summary of Actions Taken at Senate, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - NYU Graduate Faculty Members, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Conflict Resolution - Modern Approach - Exec. Action Letter, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Taggart Committee Report, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - "Method of Inference" in Foreign Language Study, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Demo of the Use of Simulation in Training School Administrators, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Teacher Supply and Demand in Public Schools, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Role Experience and Perceptions of School Principals, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Center for Field Research and School Services, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 270 5
  - Center for Field Research and School Services, undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 271 3
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Azzarelli, undated (Box 104, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 272 1
  - Deans Weekly Reports:: Baker, undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Blustain, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Coretin, undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Hartley, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Hug, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Kleinman, undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: McDonald, undated (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Memonberg, undated (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Payne, undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Spencer, undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Deans Weekly Reports: Zobrowski, undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Deans Correspondence: Buken, undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Deans Correspondence: Blustain, undated (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Deans Correspondence: Hartley, undated (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Deans Correspondence: Memonberg, undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Deans Correspondence: Payne, undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Deans Correspondence: Zobrowski, undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 273 9
  - AAUP, undated (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Academic Goals, undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Admissions: Martin Luther King, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Admissions: Summer Sesssions, undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Admissions: Reports - Garen, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Admissions: Reports, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Admissions, 1969-1970 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Analysis Sheets for Conference, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Budget Weekly Reports, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Budget Meeting, 1963-1968 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Budget Materials, undated (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Planning, Alumni and Public Relations, undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Disciplinary Committee, undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Committee to Study Role of the Faculty, undated (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Committee to Explore Possibility to Enlist Students of the School, undated (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Committee to Study Masters' Program, undated (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Policies Committee, undated (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Committee Procedures (Securing Visiting Speaker), undated (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Curriculum Requirements, 1967-1968 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Dean Group Minutes, undated (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Dean Group Minutes, undated (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Weekly Reports - OERS, undated (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Teacher Education Commission - School of Ed, 1963-1968 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - NCATE - Washington, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - NYU - Senate, undated (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - University Senate, 1962-1965 (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 274 7
  - Faculty - Meetings of the Faculty, 1961-1965 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - All Day Faculty Meeting at Gould Stuent Center, University Heights, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meeting MInutes, 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting MInutes, 1963-1964 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting MInutes, 1964-1965 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting on the Role of the School of Ed in the 60s, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - November Speech to Faculty, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting, 1963-1965 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Research Committee Report to the Faculty Council, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - School of Education Faculty Research Seminar Papers, undated (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - School of Ed Faculty Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: H, undated (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Proficiency Exam Committee, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 275 4
  - University Committee on Graduate Work, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Doctoral Research Requirements and their Effects - Giles, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - School of Ed - Committee to Study the Doctoral Program, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Ad Hoc Comm: Nursing School, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - School of Ed - Prof. Blustain, Jonah, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees - School of Ed Committee, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - School of Ed Department Art Education, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - School of Ed Department Center for Human Relations, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Community Studies, undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Center for Urban (Illegible), undated (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Center on Teaching, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Deafness Research Center, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Deafness Research Center, undated (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Deans Group, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Bromberg, undated (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Berenger, undated (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Brogdon, undated (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Buenza, undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Brookman, undated (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Cartter, undated (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Goren, undated (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Hester, undated (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Gutlain, undated (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Alex Rosen, undated (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Geo Stone, undated (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Von Guerand, undated (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Whiteman, undated (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - Childrens Report, undated (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - Development, undated (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Correspondence: A-Z, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 276 2
  - Dept. Head Meeting, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Editorial Board, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Ed. Auditorium (Remodeling), undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Ed. Assistance Center (Proposal), undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Ed. Library, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Ed. Quarterly, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Editorial Board (Education Quarterly), undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Educational Support Committee, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Encyclopedia of Ed., undated (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Ed Group Complaints, undated (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation Elementary and Secondary Education, undated (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Experienced Teacher Fellowship Program, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Faculty Welfare and Admin. Relationships, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Draft and Comments on Attitudes of Faculty Members, undated (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Index, undated (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - New Faculty Orientation, undated (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Rating Forms, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 277 0
  - Full Time Faculty, undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Faculty - Russels Report, undated (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Seminar on Inquiry, undated (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Service Food Formula, undated (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Symposium, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Salries, undated (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Faculty All-Day Conference, undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council (Special), 1969-1971 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Faculty All Day Meeting, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings, undated (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Division Folders - before Future of School Program became effective, undated (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - GSO (Division Folder), undated (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Grants and Projects (Division Folder), undated (Box 110, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 278 8
  - Industrial Arts, undated (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Inservice: Teacher Ed, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Study of Government in Education for Developmental Studies, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Institution Services, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - ISR Journal, undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - ITTP (Intensive Teacher Training Program, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - ITTP City College, undated (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Intersdisciplinary Analysis, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - International Education, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - International Students, undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Labor Relations Advisory Council, undated (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Registration Reports - Von Guerand, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Division and Departments of School of Ed for Business Ed. Dept, undated (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Ed. Research Serv., undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 279 6
  - Ambudsman, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Panama Project, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Info, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Placement Office, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Planning - Programming Budget, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Population Center, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Post Office, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - School of Ed - Presidential Committee, undated (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Presidents Council Commission, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Professional Sequence Commmission, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Prospective Teacher Fellowships, undated (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Pubic Broadcasting Lab, undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Publicity, undated (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - The Purpose of of a School of Ed, undated (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations, undated (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports Materials, 1965-1968 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - State of the School Addresses, 1965-1975 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Files: Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Files: Acknowledgement Letters, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Files: Giving, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Files: Awards, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Files: Fund Raising, 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead - President Hester, 1964-1973 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - NYS School Boards Association, undated (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Lila Rosenblum (Alumni Giving), 1969-1970 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1963-1964 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Awards (General), 1964-1969 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Acknowledgement Letters (Alumni), General, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Conference, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - Walter A. Anderson Memorial, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Alumni, List of Superintendents of Schools, undated (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - Home Economics Departmental Campaign - Exec. Committee, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 34)
  - Education Alumni Conference, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 35)
  - Alumni News, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 280 4
  - Dr. Herbert Axelrod (Correspondence), 1967-1971 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Dean's List, 1964-1970 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - NYS School Board Association, 1964-1965 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Lindback Foundation Awards, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - JDR 3rd Fund, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Maidman Project, 1969-1970 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Info: Capital Campaign, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Chester Roth, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Ettinger Awards, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Hester Speech, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Hilser Corporation, 1967-1971 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Farkas Hall, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead, Report by Pres. Hester, 1964-1973 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Alumni - Dean's List, 1963-1964 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association, 1963-1966 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Day Awards, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Fund Raising, 1963-1971 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Capital Campaign, 1964-1970 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Acknowledgement Letters, 1963-1967 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Executive Committee Meeting, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Education Alumni Board Meeting, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Evening, Nyack NY, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Meetings, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Anne Steinman (re Anastasi), undated (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Federation, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Association, Board of Directors Meeting, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - Search Committee for Dean, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 321 6
  - Administrative Structure of SEHNAP Affirmative Action, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Ross, Jerrold, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Carras, W. Gabriel, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Dean Arnold Spinner - Weekly Reports, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Sabbaticals / LOA, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Clerical Staff, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Letters, undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Resignations, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Dean Carras - Weekly Reports, undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Staffing Plans, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Staffing Plans, 1980-1982 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Screening Comm. Associate Dean for Personnel, undated (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Dean Elmer E. Baker, Jr. - Weekly Report, undated (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Baker, Elmer E., Jr. Vice Dean, 1977-1983 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Dean Carey - Weekly Reports, undated (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Carey, Patricia - Asst. Dean for Students, undated (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Travel Requests, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 322 4
  - Japan, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Federal Register, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Federal Legislation and Education in NYS, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - L. Jay Oliva, 1970-1979 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Faculty, Computer Data, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Listings - SEHNAP, undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Sunrise Semester, undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Summer Sessions, 1976-1980 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - NYU Teacher Corps, 1969-1973 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Teacher Corps NYS Network, 1977-1981 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Teacher Ed - Commit Report, undated (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Tenure Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Developmental Studies, undated (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Registration Reports, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 323 2
  - Student Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Self-Study Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 324 0
  - Student Participation, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Center for International Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Government Relations, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Seminar in University and College Administration, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - South Bronx Project, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Center for Continuing Education - Sarah Lawrence College, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga Springs Conference, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - School for Children, 1961-1964 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - School of Creative Arts, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - SRI (Scientific Resources, Inc.), 1966 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - School of Education Finance, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Office of Research Services (Reports), 1967-1969 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Senate: Spec. Meeting - Proposed Comm. On Student Participation, undated (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - University Senate, 1967-1969 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Secondary School at NYU, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Charter & By-Laws, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Taxonomy Study, undated (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Correspondence: A, 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Correspondence: B, 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Correspondence: C, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Correspondence: D, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Correspondence: E, 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Correspondence: F, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Correspondence: G, 1965-1967 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Correspondence: H, 1967-1968 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Correspondence: I, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Correspondence: J, 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Correspondence: K, 1965-1968 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Correspondence: L, 1968-1969 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 325 7
  - Faculty Correspondence: M, 1967-1968 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Correspondence: N, 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Correspondence: P, 1966-1968 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Admissions, 1963-1968 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Chancellor Chartter Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Chas. R. Kelly (Bob) Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - David G. Ryans Correspondence, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence: S, 1961-1965 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence: T, 1962-1965 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence: V, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence: W, 1962-1965 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Self-Study Committee, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Vocational & Technical Education - NYS Dept of Ed, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Waldon School, 1963-1967 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Westbury Long Island - Meeting with Rice, Superintendent of Schools, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Workshop for Principals, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Ellis White: Higher Ed. In Basket (Montclair College), undated (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Baccalaureate Services and Recept., 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Baccalaureate Planning, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Senate Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Bahamas Ed. Clinic, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Baldwin Material, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Bank Street, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Biblical Seminary, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees - School of Ed., 1963-1964 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Boys Harbor, 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Brochures (Misc. - NYU), 1964-1966 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - NYU Commencement (Excuses and Bulletins), 1967-1968 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Puerto Rico, 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Senate Meeting, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 326 5
  - Summer Session Meeting, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Savitt, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Meeting - Vermont State Board of Education, 1967 (Box 118, Folder data_value_missing_8328433700015548cd8d7d0fc0ed281a)
  - Virgin Islands Site Visit, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Virgin Islands - December 14-18, 1966, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    General Note
  - Washington Square Council, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Weekly Reports - Beaman, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Weekly Reports - Fields, 1965-1967 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Weekly Reports - Griffiths, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - NYU Urban Research and Community Services, undated (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, 1967-1968 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Correspondence: W, 1965-1967 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Mayor Lindsay - Cabinet Meeting, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Correspondence: R, 1966-1967 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Correspondence: S, 1963-1967 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland Conference - Chicago, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Ed. Leadership (Regents Advisory CEL), 1965 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Croft Educational Services Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence: L, 1962-1967 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence: M, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Hollis H. Moore Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1960-1966 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 327 3
  - Advisory Council, 1959-1968 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Am. Educational Research Journal - Kerlinger, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Defamation League - Human Relations Meeting, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Arch Award Dinner, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Attendance, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Bahamas, 1963-1964 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Center for Advanced Study of Educational Administration Annual Report, 1967-1969 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Center for Gifted Children, 1962-1965 (Box 119, Folder 9)